http://www.singularsecurity.com/privacy-policy/

Compliance Assessment
Privileged Access Management (PAM)
Compliance Assessment
Privileged Access Management (PAM)
Singular Security Privacy Policy
Singular Security, Inc. (hereafter referred to as Singular Security) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our privacy commitment to users of our website. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat provided information collected from our visitors and users.
What this Privacy Policy Covers
This privacy policy covers Singular Security’s treatment of personally and/or professionally provided information collected through our website.
This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Singular Security does not own or control, or of persons that Singular Security does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Singular Security websites link.
Collection and Use of Provided Information
You can visit our website without revealing any information. However, Singular Security needs certain information if you wish to purchase, obtain or know more about our solutions or services, register for an account, receive Singular Security newsletter, or use certain Singular Security services.
Where required, this information may include contact information and/or company contact information. Singular Security will use this information to reply to inquiries, provide requested solutions and services information, to set up a secured account, or to contact individuals regarding new solutions and services.
By accessing the services of Singular Security and voluntarily providing us with the requested information, individuals consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information
Singular Security automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page an individual requested. Singular Security may use this information to customize the advertising and content an individual may see and to fulfill requests for certain products and services. However, Singular Security does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from a person.
Singular Security also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and Singular Security assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Singular Security may disclose information provided to third parties who work on behalf of Singular Security to provide products and services requested. We will share provided information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to provided information.
Singular Security may otherwise disclose provided information when:
We have express consent to share the information for a specified purpose.
We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process.
We need to take reasonable effort to protect the personal safety of users visiting our website or defend the rights and property of Singular Security.
Consent
If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any information to Singular Security. If you have provided information to Singular Security and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify Singular Security at info@singularsecurity.com
Security
It is important to point out that no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, we safeguard provided information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.
Further, Singular Security retains provided information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Singular Security may at any time, without notice and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
For questions or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, or provided information, please e-mail us at info@singularsecurity.com
Contact
Singular Security
$$$
17601 17th Street, Suite 240Tustin, CA 92780
Phone: 714-669-1618
Phone: 714-669-1618
888-669-1618
888-669-1618
Fax: 714-669-1608
Email: info@singularsecurity.com
Latest ArticlesNew Phone Malware Signs You Up For Expensive SubscriptionsDecember 10th, 2020Some Spotify Users Reporting Possible Hacking Of Their AccountDecember 9th, 2020Social Media
© Copyright 2020 Singular Security
Privacy Policy
